[
     {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 11 and height 19?",
      "correctAnswer": "104.5",
      "options": [
        "107.0",
        "104.5",
        "102.0",
        "108.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 8 and height 21?",
      "correctAnswer": "84.0",
      "options": [
        "84.0",
        "88.0",
        "81.5",
        "86.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 19 and height 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "66.5",
      "options": [
        "66.5",
        "69.0",
        "64.0",
        "70.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 13 and height 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "13.0",
      "options": [
        "17.0",
        "15.5",
        "10.5",
        "13.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 25 and height 11?",
      "correctAnswer": "137.5",
      "options": [
        "135.0",
        "141.5",
        "140.0",
        "137.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 10 and height 11?",
      "correctAnswer": "55.0",
      "options": [
        "59.0",
        "52.5",
        "55.0",
        "57.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 11 and height 22?",
      "correctAnswer": "121.0",
      "options": [
        "118.5",
        "123.5",
        "125.0",
        "121.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 11 and height 23?",
      "correctAnswer": "126.5",
      "options": [
        "126.5",
        "124.0",
        "130.5",
        "129.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 23 and height 24?",
      "correctAnswer": "276.0",
      "options": [
        "276.0",
        "273.5",
        "280.0",
        "278.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 29 and height 21?",
      "correctAnswer": "304.5",
      "options": [
        "307.0",
        "302.0",
        "308.5",
        "304.5"
      ]
    }
]